pooltracker.com 2019-04-05

# Privacy Policy for PoolTracker

### Privacy policy

At Pooltracker we respect and protect your privacy. Our site is a safe environment for anyone who visits and purchases. We are committed to providing you with the best possible online service and experience as well as the best services. The purpose of this policy statement is to fully share with you: 

  * why the Pooltracker online shop is so secure 
  * a complete description of what we collect 
  * how we use that information 
  * how you can access or correct your information

We never rent, sell or share any information you give us. You privacy is important to us! 

**What information does Pooltracker collect, and how is it used?**

When you visit the Pooltracker.com site, we collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. This includes which pages are visited, types of products purchased, and any feedback from our visitors. We then collate this information with other pieces of information to improve our site and make your experience on the site as valuable and efficient as possible. 

On some pages (our Members Area), you can register and order services, make requests, and invite others to join. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

* Email address 
* Username 
* Password 
* Billing address 
* Phone number 
* Credit card account number 
* Titles of services you purchase from us 

**The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order, to send you reminder notices to make your picks and to send you promotions for upcoming tournaments and to use it internally for statistical reasons. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Credit Card Processing and Security**

Shopping with Pooltracker is absolutely safe - you never have to worry about credit-card safety when you are shopping at our site. We guarantee that each purchase you make is protected and safe. If fraudulent charges are ever made, you will not have to pay for them. 

Pooltracker uses the services of Authorize.net to provide the highest level of secure online transactions. Your credit card information cannot be read as it travels to our ordering system. Authorize.net maintains their own privacy and security policies. If you have questions about these services, or how they handle the information they receive, please contact Authorize.net. 

All information you enter in the Authorize.net order form will be shared with Pooltracker in order to fulfill the purchased services. This does not apply to your credit card information. We never get your credit card number. 

**How You Can Access or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in and clicking the "My Settings" link near the top of each "Members Area" page or by sending us an email. The exception, as explained above or in the "Credit Card Processing and Security" section, is your credit information, since it is not kept. **We will never ask for your Credit Card number.**

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Other**

We link to other Web sites. Any data that you supply on these Web sites is beyond our reach and will be the responsibility of the linked-to entity and not Pooltracker. We do not have access to the information you give them. Pooltracker is not responsible for the content published on these sites. 

By using the Pooltracker.com site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by Pooltracker as described in this policy. Any legal disclaimer statements (i.e., terms and conditions, etc.) on our website and in our software do not negate the promises made in the privacy policy. 

Pooltracker fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to release information about members who we believe are in violation of our content guidelines. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we reasonably believe to be unlawful. 

Pooltracker wants you to be aware that when you click on links that take you to third-party Web sites, you will be subject to the third parties� privacy policies. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, Pooltracker cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any Web site. 

We welcome comments and questions. Please contact us at support@Pooltracker.com. 

Click here to go to our home page. 

**Our 100% guarantee**

We believe in what we do. We'll gladly give you a complete refund of the purchase price, within our Site Guarantee guidelines. We always make an effort to make the customer happy in a fair and just manner. 

**Shopping with Pooltracker.com is 100% safe** \- you never have to worry about credit card safety when you are shopping at our site. We guarantee that each purchase you make is protected and safe. If fraudulent charges are ever made, you will not have to pay for them. 

**Safety in Numbers:** Pooltracker services are sold by Authorize.net, which is one of the oldest and biggest online stores on the Internet. When you purchase at Authorize.net, you'll be one of thousands of customers who have safely shopped with Authorize.net without credit card fraud. 

**Safe Technology:** Authorize.net's secure server software (SSL) is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts your credit card number, so that it cannot be read while the information travels over the Internet. 

In general, under federal law of the United States, you will not be liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges. In the unlikely event that you are subject to fraudulent charges, remember to first notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. If, for whatever reason, you are held responsible for this amount, Pooltracker.com will cover the entire liability for you, up to $50, as long as the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made from Pooltracker.com while using our secure server.
